> > 布莱恩: 现在，我想给你们看几件事情。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now, I wanna show you
a couple more things about this.
如果我希望此操作在安装时运行，那么会发生什么情况，因此当它首次呈示时
What happens if I want this to run when
it mounts, so when it first renders and
那就再也不去了
then Never again?
> > 布莱恩: 你刚才给出了一个空的数组。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Well,
you just given an empty array.
这是它的一系列依赖性，它说，我什么都不依赖，对吗 ?
This is an array of its dependencies and
it's saying, I depend on nothing, right?
>> Brian: 那么它将运行一次，然后这将不会再次更新。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So then it's gonna run once,
and then this will never update again.
> > 布莱恩: 对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Right?
因此，如果您希望它在第一次创建时运行一次，就会产生这样的结果。
So if you want it run once on what it
first creates that's how you do that.
如果需要与 J 查询插件进行集成，那么这将非常有用。
This will be useful for things like if you
need to integrate with a J query plug in.
比如当我对你和 D3感到抱歉的时候
Like when I'm sorry that's
happening to you and, or like D3,
也许是个更好的例子吧
that's maybe a better example, right?
如果你要和 D3 集成，你就需要设置所有这些东西，对吗 ?
If you have to integrate with D3 and
you need to set up all that stuff, right?
这就是你要做的
This is where you would do it.
> > 布莱恩: 然后你可以给它一个空的数组，就像，好吧，
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then you could give
it an empty array, it's like, okay,
一旦集成了，就不要再更新了，对吧 ?
once this is integrated then
don't update this anymore, right?
如果你想让它每次都更新一些东西
And then if you want it to run every
single time something updates,
把那个扔了
get rid of that.
所以现在如果我来这里
So now, if I come over here,
> > 布莱恩: 应该，
&gt;&gt; Brian: It should,
> > 布莱恩: 这里发生了什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: What is going on here?
好了好了
There we go.
> > 布莱恩: 是的，我的意思是你可以看到我创造了无限循环，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Yeah, I mean you can see
here I've created an infinite loop,
你可以看到我有， >> 布莱恩: 事实上我要阻止
you can see that I have,
&gt;&gt; Brian: In fact I'm gonna stop that so
我不喜欢我的 API
I don't crush my API.
> > Brian: 所以请不要这样做。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So don't do that please.
我要付那个账单
Cuz I'm paying that bill.
所以现在发生的事情就像
[LAUGH] So
what what was happening there is like it's
每次更新都要运行对吧
running every time something updates,
right?
这意味着每次我呼叫分离的时候都在引起更新对吧
Which means that every time that I call
separates, it's causing an update, right?
这意味着它会再次达到预期的效果。
Which means that it caught it's
scheduled that effect again.
然后再更新它们的品种
Which is then going to
update their breeds again,
这会安排另一个效果的对吧
which is gonna schedule another effect,
right?
这个无限循环的记号
Sick of this infinite loop.
所以这就是为什么他们强制执行这个， >> 布莱恩: 附属物，
So that's why actually they enforce this,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Dependencies thing,
这样你就不会陷入这种境地了对吧
so you don't get yourself
into these situations, right?
因为如果看动物，你就得看动物在那里，
Because if it depends on animal then you
should depend on animal being there and
反之亦然，您不希望导致这些无限的更新循环，
via vice-versa, you don't want to
cause these infinite loops of update,
然后这个计划又产生了另一种影响
and then that schedule in another effect.